# SOFTWARE DEVELOPER ARIEL MEJIA DEV

## CONTACT

ARIELMEJIADEV@GMAIL.COM

<u>WWW.ARIELMEJIA.DEV</u>

GITHUB.COM/ARIELMEJIADEV

GUATEMALA CITY

# **PROFILE**

I am a software developer with 5 years of experience working with back-end and frontend technologies such as PHP, Javascript, Laravel, VueJS and other technologies, I seek to collaborate in a position that allows me to create software with these technologies.

# SKILLS

- LARAVEL
- VueJS Vue router VueX
- JAVASCRIPT
- PHP
- MYSQL POSTGRES SQL SERVERGIT
- HTML 5
- CSS 3
- POSTCSS, FLEX, GRIDCSS
- SASS
- DART FLUTTER



# **EXPERIENCE**

#### SENIOR DEVELOPER

BUILDAWOW | 2018 - 2020

- Develop mainly Backend and Frontend projects using Laravel as backend technology and VueJS as frontend technology.
- Advising in technical decisions, Implementation of design patterns, TDD (test driven development) and SOLID principles in backend development.
- Add Laravel forge as our primarly.server deployment service.

#### **BACKEND DEVELOPER**

IPM | 2016 - 2018

- Development of software for internal use ( Private software, generate institutional documents, Polls, and queue flows ), using PHP as the primary language and Javascript for the frontend.
- Add new technologies at this time, Bootstrap 3 and 4, composer and Laravel 5.0 in the implementation of some projects.
- Implementing gitflow (at this time they do not use any version control)

### **EDUCATION**

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGIES AND TELECOMUNICATIONS (PENSUM CLOSED)

UNIVERSIDAD GALILEO | 2013 - 2018

#### CERTIFICATIONS

LARACAST PROFILE

HTTPS://LARACASTS.COM/@ARIELMEJIADEV

**CERTIFICATIONS LINK**